<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on WolfieZero.com</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on WolfieZero.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 22:57:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Code – I think this is the one!</title>
      <link>/blog/visual-studio-code-think-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 22:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/visual-studio-code-think-one/</guid>
      <description>I have been an avid fan of using Atom for some years now. During that time I’ve moved from text editors to IDEs and back again, always finding myself back to Atom. But I’ve started looking towards Visual Studio Code as a new tool to solve issues I’m having. It’s been quite a surprise!
Before I get going, a point to make. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a sponsored post at all and I&amp;rsquo;ve not reached out to Visual Studio Code or Microsoft for anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Hosts with Nginx</title>
      <link>/blog/dynamic-hosts-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 12:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/dynamic-hosts-nginx/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure I&amp;rsquo;m not the only person who want&amp;rsquo;s to throw up a site on the web quickly. Further the point, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to worry about configuring a server either. All I want to do is have a folder on my server that points to the domain it says and access it.
The flow should be simple. If a request for &amp;ldquo;boom.wolfiezero.com&amp;rdquo; hits my server, use the folder /var/www/boom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue November: 51 Weeks to Get Here…</title>
      <link>/blog/blue-november-51-weeks-get/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 18:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blue-november-51-weeks-get/</guid>
      <description>A year ago, I didn&amp;rsquo;t take my diabetes in a way I should have and only did the basics of what I thought I needed to. The only bits I stuck to was not to drink the sugar drinks and doing my insulin every day. I coasted on by.
The Event That was until I woke up one morning after moving the living room furniture around till 3am. During this time, I went low and only ate a candy bar to bring my sugars back up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue November for Diabetes</title>
      <link>/blog/blue-november-diabetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blue-november-diabetes/</guid>
      <description>This month is Blue November; a month to raise awareness of diabetes. It ties in with World Diabetes day on the 14th of November, which is the birthday of Fredrick Banting. He&amp;rsquo;s one of the people who co-discovered insulin!
This year sort of hold dear to me as on the 21st it will be a year since I had a seizure caused by diabetes. Though doctors didn&amp;rsquo;t think it was. I had to go through various tests that could have changed my life in a massive way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Occam’s Razor and Keeping Development Simple</title>
      <link>/blog/occams-razor-keeping-development-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/occams-razor-keeping-development-simple/</guid>
      <description>When I do any app or web build I often try to follow Occam&amp;rsquo;s Razor. It&amp;rsquo;s key to any development or design in crafting a well-built app. In my opinion anyway. The Wikipedia quote&amp;rsquo;s Occam&amp;rsquo;s Razor as:
 Among competing hypotheses, the one with the fewest assumptions should be selected.
 Keep it simple, in other words.
William of Ockham wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only person to believe in the idea of making things simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trust Your Elders! Or Rather, Experienced Developers</title>
      <link>/blog/trust-your-elders-or-rather-experienced-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 10:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/trust-your-elders-or-rather-experienced-developers/</guid>
      <description>One thing I&amp;rsquo;ve often done is take a method that somebody has developed with and changed it to suit me. Be this a full out framework or just a minor snippet. Code should always be well written and look good and be simple as possible.
That being said, there is something to think of before making any changes.
If you&amp;rsquo;re working with something by somebody who has lots more experience than you, maybe you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waffle.io – Trello and Github Issues Merged</title>
      <link>/blog/waffle-io-trello-github-issues-merged/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 12:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/waffle-io-trello-github-issues-merged/</guid>
      <description>So what if Trello met Github Issues and decided to have a child? It would most likely be Waffle.io. And you know what, I love it and I think you might too.
When I worked at Fubra, myself and few others decided to use Github Issue for our project management. Alice covers this in a blog post at Furba.com that the newer teams use in their iteration. It was an elegant solution using a tool we used already utilised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Difference Between a Website and a Web App</title>
      <link>/blog/difference-website-web-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 14:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/difference-website-web-app/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I&amp;rsquo;m asked a question in various forms.
 What is a web app and what is a website?
 I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure not a lot of web developers do struggle with this question. It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting question as the two aren&amp;rsquo;t exclusive. There isn&amp;rsquo;t a rule that says what each one is in general. So I&amp;rsquo;m going to try to lay down my thoughts on the subject and how I differentiate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinvent the Wheel, It Will Help</title>
      <link>/blog/reinvent-wheel-will-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 14:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/reinvent-wheel-will-help/</guid>
      <description>Let me start this with a mini-rant before I talk about development&amp;#8230;
The saying &amp;ldquo;You shouldn’t reinvent the wheel&amp;rdquo; I think is complete bull and a bad choice for any reasoning without research.
Look at that saying reinvent the wheel; are we expected to think that nobody has looked at the wheel and thought &amp;ldquo;I know what could improve this&amp;rdquo;? When the first wheel was invented it was thought to be a rock that was carved into something circular so early humans can push things rather than drag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hiatus is Over, I’m Blogging Again</title>
      <link>/blog/hiatus-over-blogging-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hiatus-over-blogging-again/</guid>
      <description>After a long hiatus, I&amp;rsquo;m back blogging again with a newly design version of WolfieZero.com! I decided to go for an agile approach for the site, so I&amp;rsquo;ll always be improving it. My issue is often trying to achieve perfection and it takes me forever to get something out. With this approach, I hope to give something new and try to impress! Even though I&amp;rsquo;m trying to impress, the Sass source for WolfieZero.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>